<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project #2</title>
    <link>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Project #2</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 12:48:55 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Cabana</title>
      <link>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/tacocabana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 12:48:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/tacocabana/</guid>
      <description>An Institution In a world of fast food representing poor imitations of food that could be, there stands a behemoth whom, atleast in the realm of bean and chesse tacos, not only produces food in a masterfully quick manner, but also captures the truest essence of what that food hopes to achieve. This is the true wonder of Taco Cabana. That a business, a corporate chain, could so effortlessly recreate such paramount tex-mex cuisine at countless locations with staggering consistency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layne&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/laynes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 12:46:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/laynes/</guid>
      <description>Andrew&amp;rsquo;s Opinion: Layne&amp;rsquo;s really isn&amp;rsquo;t that good Sure, it sounds good. A box of chicken strips, french fries, toast, and that amazing Layne&amp;rsquo;s sauce. But the sauce is about the only good thing. And maybe the variety of food you get for the price. Is it really worth it?
Layne&amp;rsquo;s chicken is dry. You get juicier chicken from the frozen isle at Walmart.
Layne&amp;rsquo;s chicken is greasy. If your stomach can barely handle it, you know it&amp;rsquo;s not good for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean&#39;s Opinion on Potbelly Sandwich Shop</title>
      <link>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/sean/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 11:47:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/sean/</guid>
      <description>Potbelly Sandwich Shop Potbelly is one of the best fast food sandwich shop Unlike Subway Potbelly doesn&amp;rsquo;t advertise themselves as a &amp;ldquo;create your own&amp;rdquo; sandwich place. Potbelly tries to take some of the creativity out of it by giving you a limited selection of your meat and cheese. Your creativity comes into play after the sandwich has been toasted. This is where condiments can be added. The only thing that is mandatory is Potbelly&amp;rsquo;s own hot peppers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle</title>
      <link>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/briehna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 23:59:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/briehna/</guid>
      <description>Chipotle Chipotle is a Mexican Grill fast-food restruant. Chipotle serves salads, burrritos, bowls, and tacos. You have the choice to build your own with different choose meats,rices, and beans, and sides like corn, sauces, sourcream, and etc. You have the choice of add-ons such as guacolmole and chips on the side for an extra charge. They also have a choice for vegans. Chipotle is more expensive. They don&amp;rsquo;t have as many deals as Freebirds does on Hooked but the quality of the food is better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fat Burger</title>
      <link>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/janelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://order-of-the-phoenix-project.github.io/posts/janelle/</guid>
      <description>Fat Burger Grill Located at 11907 FM 2154 Rd #101, College Station, TX 77845 Hours of Operation 11:00am -12:00am Fat Burger Grill offers flame broiled burgers of all sizes from the 1&amp;frasl;4 lb 90% lean burger to the 1 lb Bevo burger. The menu also includes turkey burgers and veggie burgers as well as ultra lean Buffalo (Bison) burgers with high omega 3. The restaurant is Aggie-owned and operated. Reviews Justin F of College Station on Yelp said: Ordered the heavyweight (1&amp;frasl;2 lb) burger combo with cheese and it was delicious!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>